GOD HAS ORDERED ALL
It is time you should be a producer not a consumer.
Tell your neighbour, 'Be a producer, not a consumer'.
This is the problem we are facing in our continent Africa.
What is it?
Instead of using our mineral resources to exchange technology,
we use it to exchange dollars and pounds.
Instead of using the mineral resources the Lord has given us,
and take it, "Hey, you need something from me?
We Africa, we carry our property, our mineral resources.
Instead of giving them and using it to receive the technology they have,
we give them and receive dollars and pounds.
We keep...
If we used these mineral resources to get technology,
nobody would embezzle money.
If there was a law that these mineral resources should not be exchanged for dollars and pounds,
but rather for technology - when I want to give something to America,
I will look at what they are good at in technology.
Give me your technology, let me give you my oil. The corruption would come to an end.
In Nigeria, for example, we have oil. Then, if in Nigeria there was a law that if any country needed this oil,
we would need to check what the other country's technology or mineral resources are.
Our own is oil - if there was a law that they give their mineral resources
while we equally give our own mineral resources, no money would be exchanged.
The country today would become a pilgrimage.
But today, what is happening to the dollars and pounds we receive?
So, Africa and other countries that are complaining that they are poor, you are not poor.
It is only that you exchange your mineral resources with dollars and pounds.
We say there is no employment, there is no job for the youths. Why?
Because dollars and pounds are not a company.
But if we use our mineral resources to exchange to receive technology from overseas,
jobs would be everywhere. The youths would have a job.
When we need money, we can sell and buy yam, cocoyam, and all other stuffs to get money.
But oil, gold, and all other mineral resources God has given you,
should not be exchanged with money.
It should not be oil for money, but oil for technology.
Say, 'Not oil for money, oil for technology'.
Tell the whole world: 'Not oil for money, oil for technology'.
GOD HAS ORDERED ALL